I caught all three of them.
Take me to the second floor cabin
Yes, I understand.
The chairman has arrived
You will be taken to your cabin.
After the chairman's escort is finished
Wait at your respective locations
hi
Come out, come out
Okay, open it
No, kids, something please
Did you feed it?
- Even an awl would be hungry
- Oh, please do something about it.
Oh, please, stay still, please.
Please
raise
Ah! Ah
Try to do something
야, 이 개새끼야
Because I can't play because of my wrist
It seems like you're just hiding
go see
Sit down
Who grabbed your wrist?
Did you make it like that?
Cha Woo-sol at the gym
He's a guy who says...
'Shita?'
I'm not a player
sour?
Hey, it's okay
How did I play today?
Don't worry, I finished it well
Sorry, sorry, chairman.
I'm afraid that I'll get into trouble because of you
- I, I, I will never, ever let something like this happen again...
- Yeah, the problem has already occurred.
There is no next
I'm not having fun with you anymore
No, over there...
Mr. Chairman, I
The chairman said...
Which of the two do you trust?
yes?
No, between my lover and my manager
Who do you give your life to?
Can you leave it to me?
ah...
Oh, not your lover but your manager?
This is my younger brother
Hey, it's my cousin!
- That fucking kid
- Oh, that's a surprise.
Oh, okay, cousin
Cousin?
Mr. Chairman
- Listen carefully
- Yes
Without saying anything
If you hold on for 10 seconds
I will save your cousin's life.
Yes?
Do you like mala-tang?
Okay
I'm sorry, Chairman.
Oh, oh, Chairman
I'm sorry, Mr. Chairman.
Mr. Chairman!
Hey, hey, hey, come to work.
Come to work, come to work!
Chairman!
- Brother, brother!
- Hey, brother!
Ah, Chairman, please save me.
- Mr. Chairman, no! No!
- Brother!
Just a part-timer
I don't think so
He had a criminal record
Cannon, you take care of it.
Bae Seok-cheon's eyes were poked
I was charged with attempted murder
Do you remember him?
The day he got out of prison
I went there and said I would pay it back
I came here with my hands full
Bae Seok-cheon is a retard
That's him
The guy with the awl
The next game is in 3 days?
Fuck!
You, let's have a match.
I didn't know at the time
What kind of storm
Has it come to us?
Oh, why?
Wonjun, are you done with your tutoring?
where are you?
I'm in the parking lot, I'm going home now, why?
No, just
Send me a text when you get home
- I don't like you.
- What are you talking about?
Hey, you keep acting like I'm your lover
It's because it's dirty
I appreciate your concern
I'm not a kid
Anyway, text me
Hey
hello?
Hey, anyway, when I got home
I'll call you, hang up
Are you okay? I'll help you.
Oh, I'm fine
Oh, it's okay, I'll help you.
Okay, then just let me go to the car.
I have a favor to ask
Yes
- ruler
- Yoon Jihee
Right?
Yes
Huh? Mr. Han
What's wrong with you? Did your business fail?
It's 'sold out', you little shit.
hey
But they've been doing this for over an hour
Are you always like that?
My big one, Chawoosol
Did you raise him? He grew up on his own.
When I first saw it, it was so weird
Just surviving on bread
I said it was a tough style
Because he's a kid who sucks at everything
Right?
Well, thanks to that, you and me
I think I'm living with my wits about me
Studying and working
admit
hey
But now we
Don't they look like a retired couple?
- what?
- No, that's right.
Looking at my grown son
You've grown up well, what are you doing, that's what I'm saying
bridge, bridge
Don't do it, don't do it, I said
- Wife
- Don't do it
- I see
Oh, seriously, don't do that!
Boy, this is killing me, damn it
No, and
Why do you always call me your wife?
huh
Oh, sir
I almost fell over because I was so frustrated, man
Oh, shit, seriously, ah
Oh, hey
Tie his legs too
Hey, hey, what is it?
Hey, sir
What the fuck
Oh, uh, are you guys here?
Because my brothers came to the gym
Woosol, you're the one shooting?
- Yes?
- Wow, you little pig.
How come you don't shoot once, once?
Lose, Mr.
Seongyong hyung, but at this time
What's up? Business...
You're not ruined, are you?
It's not ruined, it's just a waste of materials
How can both be asked the same question...
I really wish I was ruined
It's raining, you two?
- huh
- Hey, are you guys here?
Hey, Seongyong hyung, what's up with your business?
- don't
- no way...
Don't do it, you're not interested in my business.
Oh, I still
You didn't say anything, but you're making me...
And you
Didn't I tell you not to call me older brother?
He looks scarier than me
Why do you keep calling me hyung?
Oh, then
Should I call you 'hyung-ah'?
Oh, hey
Oh, don't make me laugh
I'm so hungry I could die
Let's hurry up and clean up and go
- Woosol, hurry up and get dressed.
- Yes
Let's sort it out
What the hell?
Let go, let go!
Kid, stay still.
Follow me quietly, okay?
- Jihee, Jihee
- Oh, hold on, you bitch.
Jihee, where are you?
What's wrong, Jihee?
- Hey, Yoon Ji-hee!
- Why, why?
Hey, Woosol, what’s wrong?
What's going on?
Ah, come quickly, sir.
Call again, what is it?
Is this like kidnapping?
Kidnapping? By whom and why?
Are you Cha Woosol?
Do you know Bae Seok-chan?
I'm the one who pays his salary.
Your eyes are nicer than Seokchan's
Come work with me
Oh, it's not that difficult
If you do as you are told
Money is more than you expect
You can earn more, how about that?
Sorry, I don't like it.
I want to exercise
Well, if it's attempted murder, there's no answer.
When I reach out my hand, do you grab it?
sorry
Because I'm not Seokchan
I will take care of my own life.
Hey, you fucking punk!
Driving, ugh!
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Ugh, I can't help it
Is that your girlfriend?
Your eyes are rolling right now
Calm down for now.
- I have to go.
- Calm down
Hyunwoo Yong, that guy kidnapped you.
Chawoosol! Mr.
How are you going to go alone?
What are you going to do next?
If I don't go, what will happen to Jihee?
You have to do something, bro
Hyunwoo Yong is like you said
Let's say I kidnapped her
Why did that kid kidnap me?
Think about it
It's because of me
So I'm going!
You're going crazy like this
That's what I want
So, ha
So please calm down
I'm here too
Han Seong-yong and Jeong Sang-hyeop are also there
Don't be a jerk by yourself
Let's go together, together
I told you before
I got a video call and this is what happened...
Here, no, I didn't say anything
No, fuck, the situation is like this now
I didn't say fuck
What did the police say?
The situation is unclear
There's nothing I can do
Oh, shit...
- What?
- Here I know
This is the Woongbi construction site.
Go to my car
- Let's go
- Mr. Lee
Why?
Are you going to hurt me by touching those little kids?
I'm just curious
What choice will Cha Woo-sol make?
You don't accept it?
yes
Damn, is this place really that big?
Let's split up and look for it.
Hey, Cha Woo-sol! Woo-sol!
Hey, it's dangerous to go alone.
- Two, two, torn apart
- You go with me
Hey, let's contact each other when we see each other.
- Contact me
- Be careful.
Bro, it's not here either
Ha, sir
I can't just call you, huh?
Let's go down first
Oh, I think I found it.
I think it's in here
Yeah, where is this?
Oh my, how do I explain it?
At the place we were just now
After he came in all the way
Come back to the back of the building
Come on in
Go around to the back of that building
Then turn left...
Hey, what are you talking about?
Oh, shit, hey, wait a minute
Hey, Woosol, let's go together when the kids come.
I'll go and find out
- Sanghyeop, let's go.
- He, what did he say, found it?
Hey, let's go together when the kids come.
Hey, just a minute
Don't come
Don't come, eww!
Look at this bitch's temper
Don't come!
Hey, get out of the way.
- Oh, shit.
- Jihee
Don't come!
Oh, no!
No! No!
Don't come!
Eww
Ugh!
Hey, let's wait a minute, Mr. Lee
Jihee, are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
Jihee
Ah, run away
- Huh?
- I have to run away
You little rat bastard.
Let's go, quickly, quickly.
These bastards
Fishing success
Cha Woo-sol was caught
There are two out of four scumbags
I can't see them both
What should I do?
Lee Won-jun, Yoon Ji-hee
Chawoosol
huh
Three is enough
Start shipping
What is that?
Sanghyeop, let's go by car
Woosol-ah
Woosol, wake up, okay?
Woosol, Woosol
Wonjun hyung
Jihee, are you okay? Ugh
Be quiet
Woosol, Woosol!
Come to your senses!
You fucking bastards
- Hey, you little shits!
- Woosol
- These bastards
- Woo-sol, come to your senses!
- Please stop!
- Hey, you little shits!
- Woosol!
- Stop it!